buzzaura.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy - BuzzAura

**Privacy Policy Privacy Policy of BuzzAura**

Thank you for visiting the Buzz Aura website. Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; in this policy we explain how we will treat your personal information.

 **The Information We Collect**

In some cases, we collect information regarding what pages within the site you look at, how long you look at them for and how many times you look at them. If you choose to log in the website via your Facebook account, your username and email address might be retained by us. Subsequent to this, any comments, ratings or other contributions you make to the site will be recorded and tied to this information.

 **How We Use the Information**

We may use this information to determine how this website is being used, and to gauge the popularity of different parts of the site. To determine how many times specific sections of the site are viewed so we can calculate the popularity of different establishments and so on.

 **We may use this information to track abuse if it occurs.**

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Your personal information will NOT be shared with any other third party without your explicit permission.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the Buzz Aura online policy you may contact us via support@buzzaura.com
